Xie Nanfeng.
Will you marry me?
My life
has possibilities beyond love.
Right now,
I just want to be completely myself,
and build my career.
[She's Wild Fire]
[Episode 1: A New Life After the Fall]
[Year 2011]
Chang Yongbin,
you took away the factory
I built with my own hands,
drained all my hard work,
then dumped the entire mess on me,
leaving me with massive debts.
After all we've been through
as husband and wife,
you should bear it for me.
If I could live my life over,
Chang Yongbin,
I'd make you pay a hundredfold
for all the pain you put me through.
[Copy of Patent Registration]
Sign it.
Transfer your design patent to me.
Or don't blame me
for forcing myself on you
and ruining your reputation.
I can't believe I've been reborn
20 years in the past, on this very day.
[September 1, 1991]
I studied for 12 grueling years,
and finally earned a chance
to work at the First Garment Factory.
But that very night,
a beast raped me,
stole my design patent,
and left me branded as a fallen woman.
I had no choice
but to marry Chang Yongbin.
My life hit rock bottom.
This time,
I can't let any of this happen again!
Get back here!
You wretched woman!
Where do you think you're going?
Who was the man who ruined my reputation
twenty years ago?
Chang Yongbin?
Do you know what people say about me?
They say I married a disgraced woman.
So it was you.
Mom!
I didn't kill her.
You framed me.
So it was you
who set me up in my past life.
I'll give you the factory
you've always dreamed of today.
But I'm not taking the blame for you.
I'll fight you to the death!
It was you
who sent me to hell.
Once you're dead,
as your legal husband,
I'll be entitled to a fortune.
After all we've been
through as husband and wife,
do me this favor.
It was you
who destroyed everything I had.
Chang Yongbin,
it was you
who violated me,
then tricked me into marrying you
and dragged me into hell.
You bastard!
You destroyed everything I had!
Nanfeng!
I just loved you too much.
You love me?
A scumbag like you
thinks you deserve to say that?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Why?
No, no!
This lash
is payback
for the first time
you whipped me with a leather belt
just because I burned the food.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Let me go.
You burned the food!
Y-you, don't, don't hit me!
This lash
is payback
for beating me into the ICU
just to bring your mistress,
Lin Shuang, into the house.
What are you talking about?
Don't hit me!
It hurts! Don't hit me.
This is nothing compared
to what you did to me.
Please!
This is only the interest.
Stop hitting me.
What do you want me to do?
The interest.
Say it!
What do you want me to do?
The interest, Chang Yongbin.
I'm telling you to speak!
Don't hit me anymore!
Please.
I won't do it again.
Go ahead and savor
what it's like to be me.
Stop hitting me.
Stop hitting me, Nanfeng.
I'll leave you another little reminder.
You can't be serious.
What are you going to do?
This reactive dye won't wash out.
I want everyone to see
what kind of man you really are.
No, no, no!
Nanfeng!
Xie Nanfeng!
Let go of me!
I'm not letting you get away with this!
Put that down!
Xie Nanfeng!
I'm going to kill you!
I'll kill you!
You wretched woman!
I'm going to kill you today!
Don't run!
Mr. Chu,
I heard that patent
is in the hands of an intern.
Then this factory
isn't even worth 5 million.
Stop right there!
Help!
Don't run!
Stop, you wretched woman!
You're safe now.
He won't be waking up anytime soon.
Chu Chunsheng?
[President of Chu Group, Chu Chunsheng]
President of Chu Group,
one of the top 50 companies in Hong Kong.
In my previous life,
he was Chang Yongbin's investor.
After Chang Yongbin stole my patent,
he used Chu's investment
and became the factory director.
This time,
since I met you first,
you will be
the first step toward changing my fate.
What did you do to me?
What do you think
I could have done to you?
Is this how you thank
the man who saved your life?
I remember now.
Last night,
you were the one who saved me.
So?
You want me
to thank you like this?
Then I'll take this as an invitation.